export const quizData = [
    {
        question: " 1.) imagine –> imaginative, rely –> reliable, ambition –> _____",
        options: ["ambitionful", "ambitious", "ambitiative", "ambitiabl"],
        answer: "ambitious"
    },
    {
        question: " 2.) I like people __ I don't like smoke?",
        options: ["and", "then", "but", "so"],
        answer: "but"
    },
    {
        question: " 3.) 'I like him because he`s funny'. Which is the dependent clause?",
        options: ["because he`s funny", " I like him" , "All of the above", "None of the above"],
        answer: "because he`s funny"
    },
    {
        question: "4.) 'John went to school today, but James remained at home.' This is an example of?",
        options: ["Complex Sentence", "Simple Sentece", "Compound-Complex Sentence", "Compound Sentence"],
        answer: "Compound Sentence"
    },
    {
        question: "5.) He's a waiter; she's a ___________.",
        options: ["waiteress", "waitree", "waitress", "waiter"],
        answer: "waitress"
    },
    {
        question: "6.) Happy is the _____________ of sad",
        options: ["oppose", "oppositive", "opposed", "opposite"],
        answer: "opposite"
    },
    {
        question: "7.) Do you want an orange juice ______ a guava juice?",
        options: ["and", "so", "because", "or"],
        answer: "or"
    },
    {
        question: "8.) I didn't write to him _______ he didn't write to me.",
        options: ["and", "so", "because", "or"],
        answer: "because"
    },
    {
        question: "9.) Which is a complex sentence?",
        options: ["I was late because I missed my train.", "We got up late so I missed my train.", "Both sentence A and B", "none of the above"],
        answer: "I was late because I missed my train."
    },
    {
        question: "10.) Which is a compound sentence?",
        options: ["I like walking on the beach with my dog.", "I like walking but my dog likes running.", "Both sentence A and B", "none of the above"],
        answer: "I like walking but my dog likes running."
    },
    {
        question: "11.) I like school, but dislike getting up so early",
        options: ["I like walking on the beach with my dog.", "I like walking but my dog likes running.", "Both sentence A and B", "none of the above"],
        answer: "I like walking but my dog likes running."
    },
    {
        question: "12.) 'I like school, but I dislike getting up so early'. Identify what kind of sentence is this.",
        options: ["Simple sentence", "Compound Sentence", "Complex Sentence", "Complex-Compound Sentence"],
        answer: "Compound Sentence"
    },
    {
        question: "13.) friendly –> unfriendly, honest –> dishonest, polite –> _________",
        options: ["impolite", "unpolite", "inpolite", "dispolite"],
        answer: "impolite"
    },
    {
        question: "14.) We couldn’t contact him _____ we didn’t have his number.",
        options: ["and", "so", "because", "or"],
        answer: "because"
    },
    {
        question: "15.) tired –> exhausted, small –> tiny, angry –> _________",
        options: ["furious", "annoyed", "vexed", "irritated"],
        answer: "furious"
    },
    {
        question: "16.) I could not go out last night _____ I was too busy.",
        options: ["so", "but", "and", "because"],
        answer: "furious"
    }
];